* India’s First Online Plastics Market
* **B2B Plastics**
* 
* |

#### Membership Form

×

Name\*   

CIPET alumni  
 Yes  No

Course\* 

Year\* 

Center\* 

Designation\* 

Mobile Number \* 

Email \* 

Organization Name\* 

Products/Services\* 

Address of Organization\*

Type\* \--Select Type-- Manufacturing Service Other

Sector\* \-- Select Sector -- Public Private Others

Scale\* \-- Select Sector -- Large Medium Small Others

Preferred Services from B2B\* \-- Select Sector -- Man Power RP Materials Used Machineries Mould Design Mould Services

TAN Number\* 

GSTIN\* 

Website URL\* 

Apply

#### Mould Design & Makers Tab

×

Name : Mr. Dharanitharan V

Email : dharani.tharan@hotmail.com

Contact : +91 – 98657 31606

* * *

Kalsi Moulds

H.O 399, Kohat Enclave, Pitam Pura,

New Delhi – 110 034, India

Tel: +91 – 11 – 47529392

* * *

Request Order

Name \*   

Company Name \* 

Mobile Number \* 

Email \* 

Company Location\* \--Select Company Location-- Ahmedabad Anantapur Baddi Bangalore Baroda Bhopal Chennai Coimbatore Delhi Gurgoan Hosur Hyderabad Indore Jaipur Kolkata Lucknow Mangalore Mumbai Noida Patna Pune Sonipat Thane Vapi Varnasi Others

Order Type\* \-- Select Tool -- New Moulds Mould Service Repair

Comments \*

Submit

#### Post Your Resume

×

Search

Submit

Please Wait...

Privacy & Policy
----------------

For us privacy for our valued customer is very important. We strongly believe that the personal information of our customers should not be shared with the third party without the prior consent or request from the customer. Privacy is the right of an individual and at CIPETIANPLASTEMART PVT LTD, the information of the customer such as contact no., email, addresses etc is used only for the internal purpose and not for sale. Your contact information is stored in our database and is only used to contact you during the course of your stay with us for sharing the status of your room bookings with us and then after for announcement of our latest deals and news etc. We at B2bplastic, condemn the unauthorized reach and misuse and/or disclosure of the personal information of the customer and we have strict guidelines and high security features to prevent the same. Any changes in our ‘Privacy Policy’ will be posted here on the website.

##### SECURE ONLINE PAYMENTS

For us privacy for our valued customer is very important. We strongly believe that the personal information of our customers should not be shared with the third party without the prior consent or request from the customer. Privacy is the right of an individual and at CIPETIANPLASTEMART PVT LTD, the information of the customer such as contact no., email, addresses etc is used only for the internal purpose and not for sale. Your contact information is stored in our database and is only used to contact you during the course of your stay with us for sharing the status of your room bookings with us and then after for announcement of our latest deals and news etc. We at B2bplastic, condemn the unauthorized reach and misuse and/or disclosure of the personal information of the customer and we have strict guidelines and high security features to prevent the same. Any changes in our ‘Privacy Policy’ will be posted here on the website.

Quick Links  

Follow Us On  
Facebook  
Linkedin  
Twitter

Contact  
+91 9884305236  
support@b2bplastics.com

Copyright © 2019 - All Rights Reserved[](javascript:void(0))

##### Quick Links

##### Follow us On

##### Policies

##### Contact

Copyright © 2019 B2BPlastics - All Rights Reserved[](javascript:void(0))

#### Sign In

×

Email \* 

Password \* 

Submit

#### Forget Password

×

Email \* 

Submit
